officefurniture.com 2015-05-10

# OfficeFurniture.com Privacy Policy

OfficeFurniture.com is dedicated to protecting the privacy of our customers and others who visit our website. This statement reveals our practices on collecting and distributing information and clarifies how we use and protect personal identifiable information that we obtain from our website. 

#### Personal Information

OfficeFurniture.com uses personal information so that we may better understand your needs and interests and provide superior service. On OfficeFurniture.com, you can order products, order samples or request information. On these pages, you may need to include your name, address, phone number, email address, billing and shipping information and credit card information. We may also ask you to provide us with optional information dealing with your personal or professional interests, demographics, and previous experiences with our company so that we may personalize our websites, services and communications and improve upon them. 

#### Non-personal Information (Cookies, etc.)

When you visit our site, we anonymously collect system information about your computer, such as the IP address. Cookies are small files put on your hard drive by a website. They act as a distinctive identifier for your computer, but cannot be used to recognize any individual. We use cookies to understand how our customers access our site, how often they access our site and whether or not they completed a purchase. We use this information for internal reporting and to enhance the experience of our customers at our website. 

#### Consent

By using our website you consent to the collection and use of your data and information as explained in this policy. If you enter your credit card information to purchase furniture from OfficeFurniture.com, that information is encrypted and protected with industry standard encryption software. Secure Socket Layer technology (SSL) is used to guard such information and assure you that credit card transactions are secure. We protect our databases using numerous physical, technical and procedural measures and restrict access to your information by unauthorized persons. Our information systems are preserved behind a software firewall to separate them from access by other networks connected to the Internet. All information transmitted through OfficeFurniture.com is maintained on our secure server. Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology is the electronic commerce standard for securing information as it is sent over the Internet. SSL technology is formulated to encrypt your information, and thus prevent an unauthorized party from viewing and downloading this material. Your web browser should display a web address with an "https" prefix, signifying that the SSL technology is functioning when using specific portions of our site (such as the checkout process). You can click on the Norton Secured logo below to verify that our SSL Certificate is valid.       [ ](https://www.scanalert.com/RatingVerify?ref=www.officefurniture.com) OfficeFurniture.com has been able to grow and expand its product line with its direct marketing efforts. In order to reach customers who would benefit from our products we do rent other companies' customer lists and, in turn, we occasionally rent our customer list to carefully selected companies. Information shared in this process consists only of company, name and address. **OfficeFurniture.com does NOT rent or sell email addresses or phone numbers.** Your email address and phone number will only be used for order confirmations, to communicate about your order and for the company's email newsletters. We appreciate your business and want to keep you as a valued customer of OfficeFurniture.com. If you would prefer we not share your information with other companies, please [email us](http://www.officefurniture.com/Contact-OfficeFurniture-com.aspx) (please allow 4 – 6 weeks for this process). If you would like to opt-out of receiving our email newsletters, please [email us](http://www.officefurniture.com/Contact-OfficeFurniture-com.aspx). We also provide your information to trustworthy organizations that assist in completing your order. These organizations include companies that validate and process credit card transactions, deliver your packages, schedule and perform product installations and manage service programs. It is possible that we may share your information with companies who help us analyze sales data, maintain our records, and provide other services for OfficeFurniture.com . We may also disclose your information to companies that act on our behalf and at our guidance to inform you of other OfficeFurniture.com products and services. These companies may conduct customer satisfaction surveys and manage additional customer services and benefits for us. These third parties are only authorized to use your information to execute their contractually assigned functions. We may allow third parties, such as Google, to place a cookie on your computer. After you visit our website, we may use a third party's service to display our ads when you visit another website. You may opt-out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). If you would prefer to be excluded from the customer list that we occasionally rent to other companies, please [email us](http://www.officefurniture.com/Contact-OfficeFurniture-com.aspx) (please allow 4 – 6 weeks for this process). To opt-out of receiving emails from us containing promotions and product updates, please [email us](http://www.officefurniture.com/Contact-OfficeFurniture-com.aspx). It is the duty of OfficeFurniture.com to safeguard the online privacy of all its visitors, including children. We do not knowingly collect information about children or sell products to children. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not consciously gather any information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you must have a parent or guardian aid you in using OfficeFurniture.com. If you have any questions regarding the privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your interactions with this site, please contact us by [email](http://www.officefurniture.com/Contact-OfficeFurniture-com.aspx) , by phone at 800-933-0053, or in writing to: OfficeFurniture.com  
735 N. Water St. Ste. 400  
PO Box 510050  
Milwaukee, WI 53203-0017
